tattootribes.com 2010-05-22

# TattooTribes.com Privacy Policy

Last Revised: August 21, 2009 

This privacy policy ("Policy") explains how personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by TattooTribes.com("TT", "we" or "us") with respect to your use of the web site located at www.tattootribes.com or other sites as may be owned, managed or controlled by us from time to time (the "Site") so you can make an informed decision about using the Site. **We reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy at any time. We will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on the privacy policy the date it was last updated. We encourage you to review this Policy from time to time to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.**

## WHAT IS PERSONAL INFORMATION?

As used herein, the term "personal information" means information that specifically identifies an individual (such as a name, address, telephone number, mobile number, e-mail address, or other), and information about that individual's location or activities, such as information about his or her use of the Site, when directly linked to personally identifiable information. A user name may be personal information if it includes personally identifying information such as a first and last name. Personal information also includes demographic information such as date of birth, gender, geographic area and preferences when such information is linked to other personal information that identifies you. Personal information does not include "aggregate" information, which is data we collect about the use of the Site, services or users, from which individual identities or other personal information has been removed. In other words, information about how you use a service may be collected and combined with information about how others use the same service. Aggregate data helps us understand trends and our users' needs so that we can better consider new features or otherwise tailor our Site. This policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of aggregate information. 

## WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

Active Collection.
    Personal information may be collected in a number of ways when you visit our Site. We may collect certain information you voluntarily provide to us which may contain personal information. For example, we may collect your name and email address when you register to our feeds or contact us by e-mail or other means for any reason such as entering our free tattoo lottery (we need to send you an email to inform you about lottery results, and asking for more informations on your request in case you win). 
Passive Collection.
    When you use the Site, some information is also automatically collected, including but not limited to your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your operating system, the browser type, the address of a referring web site, and your activity on the Site. We treat this information as aggregate information only.

We may automatically collect certain information through the use of "cookies". Cookies are small data files that are stored on a user's hard drive at the request of a Web site to enable the site to help users have a smoother experience, by keeping their language of choice and similar behaviours. Informations provided may be used, among other things, to better understand the usage and visitation of our Site. For third party ads policies on our site we suggest you to check [Google's Adsense privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). However, if a browser is set not to accept cookies or if a user rejects a cookie, some portions of the Site and the Service may not function properly. For example, you may not be able to keep your desired language. 

## HOW DO WE USE THE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT?

In general, we use personal information we collect to process your requests, to provide you with information or services you request, to inform you about other information, events, promotions, products or services we think will be of interest to you, to facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, the Site, and for the purpose for which the information was provided. For example, we may use the information we collect: 

  * to send you a welcoming email and to contact you about your use of the Site and to provide other services or information you request;
  * to respond to your emails, submissions, comments, requests or complaints;
  * to request feedback and to enable us to develop, customize and improve the Site and our publications and services;
  * to contact you about our or a third party's services, products, activities, special events or offers and for other marketing, informational, product development and promotional purposes; 
  * to personalize and improve the Site, site content and features and your experience on the site, such as providing ads, content or features to match your profile and interests;
  * to notify contest winners; and 
  * for the specific purpose for which the information was provided. Personal information provided online may be linked together or merged with other personal information so that we may better understand your needs and inform you about our products or services and those of our partners. In addition, if we receive information from third parties with whom we have business relationships, we may combine this information with the other personal information we maintain about you. In either case, this Policy governs this information. 

## SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will not share the personal information we collect from you through this Site with third parties except as described in this Policy, as it may be revised from time to time. We may share personal information with vendors, consultants and other service providers (“Service Providers”) who are engaged by or working with us in connection with the operation of the Site or the Service and who need access to such information to carry out their work for us, such as web hosting services. In some cases, the Service Provider may be directly collecting the information from you on our behalf. We may also share personal information with other third parties when you give us your consent to do so. We are not responsible for the actions of Service Providers or other third parties, nor are we responsible for any additional information you provide directly to these Service Providers or other third parties, and we encourage you to become familiar with their practices before disclosing information directly to them. Note that nothing herein restricts the sharing of aggregate information, which may be shared with third parties without your consent. 

We may disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are lawfully authorized or required to do so, or that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate to comply with the law or with legal process or authorities, respond to any claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of our users, our employees or the public, including without limitation to protect our users from fraudulent, abusive, inappropriate or unlawful use of our Site. Information about our users, including personal information, may also be disclosed or transferred as part of, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition or in any other situation where personal information may be transferred as one of the business assets of TT. 

You understand that when you use the Site, information you post in any private areas on the Site, as well as any information you share with individuals through the Site, will be available to other users who you have permitted to view such information, and any information posted on any publicly accessible areas will be publicly available. We recommend you be cautious about giving out personal information to others or sharing personal information in public or private areas of the Site. We are not responsible for the actions of any third parties with whom you share personal information. 

## WHAT STEPS DO WE TAKE TO PROTECT PERSONAL INFORMATION ONLINE?

We have endeavored to put into place reasonable security measures in an effort to protect personal information while it is under our control. Your account information is accessible online only through the use of a password to our administrators only. 

## WHAT CHOICES DO YOU HAVE REGARDING THE USE OF YOUR INFORMATION?

You may "opt out" of receiving email from our RSS feeds service or any other communications by unsubscribing from our feeds or sending a mail to [info@tattootribes.com](mailto:info@tattootribes.com). 

## LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES

Our web site may contain links to other web sites. Any personal information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of web sites to which we link. Links from our web site to third parties or to other sites are provided for your convenience. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information. 

## HOW CAN YOU CORRECT AND UPDATE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION OR OBTAIN ADDITIONAL INFORMATION?

If you have any questions or comments about this Policy or the practices relating to the Site, or you wish to correct or delete any personal information we have collected, please contact us at [info@tattootribes.com](mailto:info@tattootribes.com), and we will endeavor to respond to your inquiry or to correct, update or remove the personal information you have provided us as you indicate to the extent possible. 

## PROPERTY OF DESIGNS

Full rights on every design published on TT are retained by the artist who prepared the designs and by the persons whom the designs were prepared for, including the right to pubblicise them and use them commercially. Generally, usage of featured designs is allowed for free, non commercial use. Different uses may be allowed only upon written consent from the artists.
